Hey, it's popcorn time. In case you guys haven't already seen it, Anthropic released a series
of ads taking pot shots at OpenAI, specifically the fact that they'll be including ads in their
AI subscriptions, at least on some tiers. And the ads absolutely killed it; they're hilarious
and they are perfectly in sync with how Anthropic actually works. And I don't think Anthropic
could have expected a better outcome, especially when Sam Altman took to responding, first by
acknowledging how funny the ads were, but then spending another 11 paragraphs effectively
coping with the ads. Now, obviously, one of the most beautiful parts of this entire fiasco is
that both the personalities of these companies are now amply evident. Claude Anthropic,
sort of, somewhat cool and with taste, and OpenAI ChatGPT just a little autistic, I guess.
For me, the most exciting bit was the fact that this reminded me of the good old days of
macOS vs PC, or of course, Pepsi vs Coke. Those kind of ad rivalries were really good for
everybody involved. I think it'll be great, and would have been probably better if Sam Altman
had just taken the L and responded in kind with an ad of his own. And there's quite a few
pieces he could have actually picked up on, the fact that Anthropic has been extremely sketchy
with regard to limits. They were reasonably facist in making Peter Steinberg change his app's
name, though I'm guessing maybe that's a little unfair. But even so, it's definitely something
that the OpenAI team could have run with to create something fun and interesting. I think all
in all, I am really hopeful that we'll see more of these kinds of ads and people taking pot shots
at each other so that there are more popcorn moments in our life. I think we need more of that.
Yep, so see you in the next one.